I have an embryonic knob and I have a cavity, the blastocoel.
私には胚芽のボタンと、胚盤胞という空洞があります。
The moment I enter the mucosa, a second cavity appears.
私が粘膜に入ると、第二の空洞が現れます。
And there, I have two types of cells that exchange.
そしてそこには、2種類の細胞が交換し合っています。
One that looks at the old cavity, and at that moment, we start talking,
一つは古い空洞を見ており、この時点で私たちは話し始めます。
for Blechmidt, simply of an endocyst,
ブレヒミットにとっては、単に内嚢（endocyst）と呼ぶか、
or, in classical embryology, of an epiblast and a hypoblast.
あるいは古典的な発生学では、上胚葉（epiblast）と下胚葉（hypoblast）と呼びます。
The moment now I'm going to have the third chamber appear,
今、第三の部屋が現れるとき、
it will have a new system.
新しいシステムが生まれます。
It is therefore a differential growth rate between the outside and the inside.
それは、外側と内側の間の成長速度の差です。
Inside, I grow a little less fast because the trophic skin arrives less fast, that's all.
内側では、栄養膜の皮膚が届くのが遅いため、成長が少し遅くなります。それだけです。
If I feed you much faster and there, you will eat less fast than fast.
もし私があなたにずっと速く食べ物を与えたら、あなたはそこでは速く食べるよりも遅く食べるでしょう。
At the level of my tissue, there is an important phenomenon.
私の組織のレベルでは、重要な現象があります。
that will appear, and there I will induce
それは現れ、そして私は誘導します。
new information, this is what we call
新しい情報、それは私たちが呼ぶものです。
early metabolic fields,
初期の代謝場、
of permeation, of permeation
浸透、浸透、
and infusion in the trophic
そして栄養供給における注入。
information supply.
情報の栄養。
In other words, an organization
別の言葉で言えば、組織化。
of how the information
情報がどのように、
trophic,
栄養的に、
so how this primitive
つまり、この原始的な食べ物が、
food
原始的な
distributes itself
どのように分配されるか。
in the tissues
組織内で、
to transform them.
それらを変換するために。
Okay? For that, Blechmidt understood how it happened
いいですか？このため、ブレヒミットはそれがどのように起こるかを理解しました。
and he introduced new notions that are only found in biodynamic embryology,
そして彼は、生体力学的発生学にのみ見られる新しい概念を導入しました。
that information is distributed both in a way, what we call in a field
情報が、私たちが「場」と呼ぶものの中で、同時に、
of permeation, of permeation or infusion.
浸透、浸透、または注入によって分配されること。
What does that mean?
それはどういう意味ですか？
I take a layer of cells. Trophic information arrives.
細胞の層を取ります。栄養情報が届きます。
now in a much
今では、より具体的な方法で、分極した方法で。
more specific, polarized way
もしあなたが小さな絵を見たなら、
you saw that there is a zone
あなたは領域があるのを見たでしょう。
that connects to the outside
それは外部とつながっています。
at first it was everywhere
最初はどこにでもあった
and in the appearance of my vitelline
そして私の空洞の出現において
cavity, of my amniotic
卵黄嚢、私の空洞
cavity and of my external
羊膜と私の外胚葉
coelom, it organizes what we call
それは胚柄と呼ばれるものを組織します
an embryonic pedicle
それは胚柄を組織します
that is to say that the trophic information
つまり、栄養情報は
no longer comes from everywhere
もはやどこにでも来るわけではありません
but it comes in an oriented
しかし、それはある方法で来ます
way. Now, it organizes itself. I can't reach everyone, I arrive
方向付けられています。さて、それは組織化されます。私は皆が到着するのを見ませんでしたが、私は
from one side. This side is called the embryonic pedicle. If I look
到着します
at a group of cells
細胞のグループ
that will receive food, we find that it will arrive in three different ways
食べるものを受け取る細胞のグループは、それが3つの異なる方法で到着することに気づきます
from the embryonic
異なる
pedicle. One, the information can
胚柄から。1つは、情報が
pass along the membrane, along
膜に沿って、膜に沿って
the membranes.
膜に沿って通過します。
It passes along in a parallel, linear way, it
それは平行に、直線的に通過し、それは
carries the permeation field.
透過場を運びます。
It can also pass between the cells.
それは細胞間を通過することもできます。
It happens like that.
それはこのように起こります。
But there, the information, this time, becomes permeation between
しかし、ここでは、情報が、今回は、私の細胞間の透過になります。
my cells.
私の細胞。
Third step, the cell is there, which is underneath.
第三段階、細胞はそこにあり、その下にある。
Now, it's the one that wants to eat.
今、食べたいのは彼女です。
And this corresponds to a metabolic field of infusion.
そして、これは注入の代謝場に対応します。
Did you follow that?
これについていきましたか？
This will introduce a very important movement
これは非常に重要な動きを導入します
which means that we will go from completely the zygote now to a primitive fetus.
それは、私たちが今や接合子から原始胎児へと完全に移行することを意味します。
At the beginning, we can say that the trophic information is a bit general
当初、栄養情報は少し一般的だと言えます
like that.
このように。
There is no real link yet.
まだ本当のつながりはありません。
But the moment I have this passage of my...
しかし、私のこの通路がある瞬間、
We blast cells into a vitelline cavity and an external coelom.
私たちはそれらを卵黄嚢と外胚葉にブラストします。
Something else happens.
もう一つ起こることがあります。
We see here that all of a sudden, I have a concentration here.
ここで、突然、ここに集中があることがわかります。
There is no longer a link with all this small tissue,
この小さな組織全体とのつながりはもうありません。
these small masses and the external part.
これらの小さな塊と外側の部分。
It is necessary to form later the placenta, all the mess.
後で胎盤、すべての混乱を形成する必要があります。
And this is called the embryonic pedicle.
そして、これは胚柄と呼ばれます。
Or we could say the primitive umbilical cord.
あるいは原始的なへその緒とでも言いましょうか。
It's a trophic place.
ここは栄養の場です。
And there, there is this organization of metabolic movements that
そしてそこには、これから起こる代謝運動の組織化があります。
will happen.
これから起こる。
That is to say, if I now take an embryo at this stage, I will
つまり、もし私が今、この段階の胚を取り上げるとしたら、私はそれを描きます。
draw it, like this.
このように描きます。
So I have a layer of cells that we will call the amniotic cavity.
つまり、羊膜腔と呼ばれる細胞の層があります。
I have a layer of cells underneath that will be called...
その下には、卵黄嚢と呼ばれる細胞の層があります。
the Vitelline cavity, the whole, here
卵黄嚢腔、全体がここにあります。
above, I can say that I have a layer of cells
上には、細胞の層があると言えます。
that will form epiblasts, below, hypoblasts, here, the
それは上胚葉を形成し、下には下胚葉、ここに全体があり、
whole, and connected to an embryonic pedicle
そして胚膜に接続されています。
and the whole is in a cavity that we call
そして全体は、私たちが呼ぶ腔の中にあります。
the external coelom, okay?
外体腔、よろしいですか？
at that moment, we see that there is a trophic source that is
その瞬間、私たちは栄養源が
organized from the outside
外側から内側へと組織化されているが、極性を持っていることがわかります。そして
to the inside, but which is polarized. And
内側へ、しかしそれは分極しています。そして
it is there that we observe a movement
ここで私たちは、極性によって生じる動きを観察します。
due to the polarity, that is to say that the upper part was
極性によって、つまり上部はすでに
already here at a
すでにここにあり、より大きな代謝活動を持っています。
greater metabolic activity.
より大きな代謝活動。
Due to its previous position, the metabolic activity is
その前の位置によって、代謝活動はこのように行われます。
done like this.
このように行われます。
The information, it is done there,
情報はそこで、
more preferentially first in a field of permeation.
まず浸透の場において、より優先的に行われます。
At the same time, I have a central metabolic field
同時に、私には中心的な代謝場があります。
of permeation and of...
浸透と、そして
infusion
注入の
and of
そして
permeation.
透過の。
But it organizes
しかし、それはこの代謝運動を組織化します。
this metabolic movement
この代謝運動を組織化し、
to make a movement
胚の動きをこのようにします。
that my vitelline cavity
私の卵黄嚢腔が
moves
前方に移動し、
and my amniotic
そして私の羊膜腔が
cavity
羊膜腔が
moves forward.
前方に移動します。
backwards, like this, and this movement will introduce
後ろに、このように、そしてこの動きが
within my germinal disc an S-shape.
私の胚盤葉の中にS字の形を
That is to say that by this movement, the tissue that was initially flat, it
導入します。つまり、この動きによって、
will form a tissue that will form a movement like this. By
元々平らだった組織が、
the metabolic activity
このように動く組織を形成します。
that led to the acquisition.
獲得を導いた。
Vitelline cavity forward and vitelline cavity backward, but in growth.
前方に卵黄嚢、後方に卵黄嚢、しかし成長の中でのこと。
Amniotic cavity forward and vitelline cavity backward, but in growth.
前方に羊膜腔、後方に卵黄嚢。
Amniotic cavity in front, vitelline cavity behind.
平らな円盤が見えますか？
You see the flat disc?
羊膜腔、卵黄嚢、胚柄、
Amniotic cavity, vitelline cavity, embryonic pedicle, external coelom.
それが外側の人間です。
What is the error between these two drawings?
これら2つの絵の間違いは何ですか？
This must be much larger than there.
これはあそこよりもずっと大きくなければなりません。
There we see as if it were the same.
そこでは同じように見えます。
That's true.
これは非常に重要です。通常、彼らがこの絵で犯した間違いは、私がほとんど切り取って、この絵を小さく作り直し、より正確な視点を得るためにずっと大きくするべきでした。
It is very important, normally the error they made in this drawing, I should almost cut out, redo
なぜなら、ここに形成される私の外側の細胞層と、
this drawing smaller and make it much larger to have a more accurate vision.
胚盤胞の代わりに卵黄嚢になる私の卵黄嚢の間のこの通路で、
Because it is in this passage, between my external coelom that is created here, and
私の膜が描かれるからです。
my vitelline cavity that becomes vitelline instead of the blastocoel, that
そして、この膜の中で、私の...による浸透の動きがあります。
my pedicle is drawn.
注入可能なものが届くと、それはここでさらに上に発達し、
And in this pedicle, I have a movement of permeation by my...
それは私の羊膜腔を前方に動かします。
infusion capable that arrives ok it develops further up here
少し下の方に、
it brings
それは傾きを作り、この傾きの動きが、
a forward movement of my amniotic cavity ok slightly
私のエピブラストとエンドブラストの中にS字の形を作ります。
less below
私のエピブラストとエンドブラストの中に。